Bridge Line Historical Society; Collection mss129
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Bridge Line Historical Society Collection
1870-2020
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
mss129
37.1 cubic ft.
The collection consist of the Bridge Line Historical Society's newsletter, as well as original maps, drawings, and related material documenting the Delaware & Hudson Railway, a railroad that operated in the northeastern United States.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
Non-newsletter items in this manuscript group were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives in 2006, 2007, and 2015. Newsletters are transferred on a monthly basis.
Biographical History
The Bridge Line Historical Society (BLHS) was founded in 1990 to document the history of the Delaware & Hudson Railway, a railroad that operated in the northeastern United States and was known as "The Bridge Line" to New England and Canada. Delaware & Hudson was founded in 1823 as a canal company and sold in 1990 to Candian Pacific Limited. The BLHS was established by individuals with ties to Delaware & Hudson who sought to preserve that railroad's identity.
Scope and Contents
The collection includes the BLHS's newsletter, The Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin, as well as maps, drawings, and related material documenting the Delaware & Hudson Railway. Two oversize boxes are present in this collection that contain pins, a Pullman Company tea towel, a plate with the inscription The Empire State Express, as well as cash books.
Separated Materials
The archivist transferred several monographs to the book division of Special Collections. They will be catalogued and included in Minerva, the University Library Catalog.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is arranged into three series:
Series 1: Administrative and Subject Files, 1907-1981
Series 2: Maps, Blueprints, and Drawings, 1870-2004
Series 3: Newsletters, 1991-2017
Railways; Locomotives-History; Railroads-Equipment and supplies; Railroads-New York (State)-History; Maps; Newsletters; Files by subject; Delaware and Hudson Railway Company; Bridge Line Historical Society
- Administrative and Subject Files, 1907-1994; 1; 4.78 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically
  Scope and Contents
  This series is comprised of log books, receipts, account books, correspondence and other administrative documents. Two oversize boxes are present in this series that contain pins, a Pullman Company tea towel, a plate with the inscription The Empire State Express, as well as cash books.
  - Agreement Between the New York Central Railroad and Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agreement for Sidetrack with Hoyt Lumber Company and Correspondence, 1924 March 19 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    General
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001076
  - Amtrack Brochures, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Amtrak "Fun N Games" Activity Booklet, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Amtrak Penn Central: New York-Buffalo-Toronto One Way Adult Coach Fares, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Amtrak Postcards and Brochure, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Assorted List of Employees and a D&H Poster, 1973; Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Numbers: BLA001096, BLA001094, BLA001091, BLA001295, and BLA001086
  - Booklet on Railroad History, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Calendar, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Camelback Locomotives: Steam Locomotives of Yesteryear, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Cash Book O.R.C., 1939-1948 (Oversized 2)
  - Comparison of Weights, Thicknesses, and Costs of ARMCO, Concrete, and Cast Iron Pipe, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001117
  - Corporate History Chart of Delaware and Hudson Company as of June 30, 1916, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000904
  - Cross Tie Renewal Chart: Susquehanna Division, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Deed from Catharine Ryan to Delaware and Hudson Canal Company, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Deed from Orlanzo Merchant and Wife to Delaware and Hudson Canal Company, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Accounting and Passenger Departments, 1947; 1949 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000148
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Adoption Notice, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Agreement Governing Hours of Service and Working Conditions, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000136
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Application for Foreign Line Trip or Reduced Rate Transporation, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000150
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Auditor of Revenue- Ticket Collections, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000143
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Certificates of Membership, 1984; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Claim of F.W. Woolworth Co., 1960 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Numbers: BLA001079; BLA001080
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Claim of National Army Stores, 1961 July 25 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001078
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Conductor's Report of Cash Collected, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000138
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Conductor's and Steward's Remittance Slip, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000144
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Conductors' Train Book, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Corporate History, Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Correspondence and Memoranda, 1916; 1920; 1927; 1930 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000126
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Crossing Watchmen, Champlain Division, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001095
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Envelope Addressed to Joseph E. Manell, Conductor, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000157
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Equiment Trust Indenture and Correspondence, 1907; 1919 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000127
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Form 1984 R.R.B., Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000155
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: General Specifications for Alterations to Restaurant and Subway Located in the Troy Union Station, Associated with Map #57, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Industrial and Real Estate Department, Map Showing Land at Dresden, NY with Correspondence, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001077
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Inter-Office Memoranda, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000130
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Inter-Office Memoranda, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000131
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Inter-Office Memoranda, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000128
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Inter-Office Memoranda, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000129
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Inter-Office Memoranda and Notes, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Lease for Land in Dresden, NY and Correspondence, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001075
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: List of Bridges, 1953 (Flat-file 2)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001327
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Local Freight Tariff Naming Switches Charges, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000133
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Local and Interdivision Passenger Tariff and Supplement to Tariffs Indicated on Page 2, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000146
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Locomotive Inspection Report, Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000137
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Land Agreement to William Catlin with Correspondence, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001070
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Land Agreement Near Dresden with Copy of Deed, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001045
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Land Near Port Henry with Correspondence, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001049
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Clayton W. Allendorph with Correspondence, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001064
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Mrs. Oscar Bapp with Correspondence, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001036
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Burr Benjamin with Correspondence, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001037
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Charles H. Brandt and William J. Brant with Correspondence, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001047
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Agreement for Lucien H. Burlingame with Correspondence, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001046
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Maurice Chevalier with Correspondence, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001042
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Dock and Coal Company, Inc. with Correspondence, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001050
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Edward Coughlin, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001055
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map for Lease Agreement to J.R. Crammond with Correspondence, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001072
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Cubitas Iron Ore Company with Correspondence, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001052
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Joanne Curtis with Correspondence, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001034
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Charles Dery with Correspondence, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001056
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Wilbur J. Dobson with Correspondence, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001048
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map for Lease Agreement to Peter Ducharme with Correspondence, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001073
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Joseph Frankovic with Correspondence, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001035
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for O.C. Gould with Correspondence, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001059
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Walter L. Hills and H.J. Lamoureux with Correspondence, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001038
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease for Agreement for Kelleher Corporation, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001074
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Charles Lethbridge with Correspondence, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001044
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map of Lease Agreement for License for Wire Crossing with Correspondence, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001066
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map for Lease Agreement for Margaret C. Luther with Correspondence, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001071
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for McGinness Brothers, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001061
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Maude L. Parker with Correspondence, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001041
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map for Lease Agreement for John Petty, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001067
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Port Henry, NY with Correspondence, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001057
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Joseph Provost with Correspondence, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001043
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map of Lease Agreement for Winifred C. Steel, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001040
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map for Lease Agreement for Samuel Ulcher with Correspondence, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001069
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map for Lease Agreement for Samuel C. Ulcher with Correspondence, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001065
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Jacob Van Amerongen with Correspondence, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001039
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Walter L. Wein, Joseph G. Frankovic and John Deley with Correspondence, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001063
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Lease Agreement for Charles E. White with Correspondence, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001033
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Port Henry Map with Correspondence, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001054
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Map Showing Track Changes in Vicinity of Watervliet with Correspondence, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000937
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Material Requisition or Transfer Order, Undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000140
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Memoranda and Correspondence, 1917-1918; 1948-1951 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000125
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Memoranda and Correspondence, 1918-1920; 1925; 1928 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000124
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Memorand and Train Line Schedules, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000160
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Office of the Superintendent of Transportaion, Special Notice in Connection with Circular No. 14, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001081
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: P.S. Division, C.T.C. "QS" to "GR" Track Changes at Globe Silo Co. and New Main Line Turnout, South End of Unadilla, NY with Correspondence, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000967
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: P.S. Division, C.T.C. "QS" to "GR" Track Changes in Vicinity of Unadilla, NY with Correspondence, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000968
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Passenger Conductor's Wheel Report, Undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000139
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Record of Fire Patrolmen, Undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001090
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Record of Rock Watchmen, Undated (Box 1, Folder 89)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Numbers: BLA001088 and BLA001089
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Remittance Envelope for National Commerical Bank and Trust Company, Undated (Box 1, Folder 90)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000153
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Report of Passengers Carried and Pullman Space Occupied, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000142
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Report of Passengers Carried and Pullman Space Occupied, Undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000141
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Sleeping Car Envelope Form SCE-1, Undated (Box 1, Folder 93)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000152
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Susquehanna Division, Track, Signal and Telephone Arrangements Between Unadilla Station and Mile Post A-86 with Correspondence, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000951A
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Third and Fourth Subdivision Roster of Engineers, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000132
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Thumb Nail Guide for Station Agents and Station Employees, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001068
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Working Memorandum No. 3, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000917
  - Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Working Memorandum No.26, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000919
  - Envelope for Mileage and Scrip Coupons Collected, Undated (Box 1, Folder 99)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000154
  - Estimate of Cost of Proposed Under-Crossing at Lockwood Highway, About 1 Mile South of Ninevah, Undated (Box 1, Folder 100)
    Other Identification Number: 12-4529
  - Form for Tickets Honored But Not Collected, Undated (Box 1, Folder 101)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000156
  - Grand Central Terminal: City Within the City, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Handwritten Material List Referencing Bridge No. 8 from Pennsylvania Division, 1948 (Oversized 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000102; Other Identification Number: 66-27236
  - Hot Box Servo Detector Correspondence and Newsletters, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000948
  - Hot Box Servo Detector Performance Slips, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Inventory of Equiment as of March 1, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000167
  - Inventory of Equiment as of March 1, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000168
  - Inventory of Equiment as of March 1, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000169
  - Inventory of Equiment as of March 1, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000170
  - List of Tools for Stone Ballasting: Force of 100 Men, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000991
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1972 February 1-March 21 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1972 August 22-1973 January 18 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1973 June 12-August 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1973 September 20-November 7 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1974 February 1-March 12 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1974 March 12-April 20 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1974 April 20-May 28 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1977 April 13-May 20 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1978 April 25-May 31 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1978 July 9-August 14 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1978 August 15-September 22 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1978 September 22-October 30 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1978 October 30-December 5 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1978 December 6-1979 January 13 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1979 January 13-February 17 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1979 February 17-March 24 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1979 March 25-May 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1979 August 20-September 27 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1979 September 27-November 3 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1980 June 28-August 9 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1980 August 10-September 23 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1980 November 5-December 20 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1981 May 28-July 4 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1981 July 5-August 15 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity, 1981 October 31-December 12 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Log Book Containing Business Activity of the Paint Shop, 1971 February 23-1973 January 5 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000206
  - Log Book Containing Contact Information and Events, 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000207
  - N.Y.G.R.R. Signal Department: Rods and Lugs for Double Slip, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - National Railway Bulletin Vol. 57-59, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - New York Central Headlight Magazine, 1959-1960; 1975; 1977-1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)